<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to My Page! on Gloria (Yujia) Deng</title>
    <link>/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to My Page! on Gloria (Yujia) Deng</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>When Can You Save the Most on Eggs?</title>
      <link>/portfolio/when-can-you-save-the-most-on-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/when-can-you-save-the-most-on-eggs/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Tengyart on Unsplash 
Introduction Omelette, scrambled eggs, fried eggs, egg sandwhich, and many more receipes use eggs as an ingredient. There is always a demand for eggs, and if you have not noticed, groceries stores adjust egg prices regularly based on the market. Yes, there is a market for eggs! Egg and egg products - shell eggs, liquid eggs, milk, cheese, etc - are like stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investment Strategies Analysis</title>
      <link>/portfolio/investment-strategies-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/investment-strategies-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Client A (male, age 50) will have a constant cash flow of $100,000 annually for the next 10 years and he is trying to use those money to make investments. His main goal is to have some level of protection and potential wealth growth at the same time.
He is given 3 strategies:
A 20 year-term product which costs $300 per month with $2,000,000 death benefit + the rest of the money will be allocated in the stock market and follows the trend of S&amp;amp;P 500 An investment product with 3% guaranteed return which yielded 5% return about half of the time (3% for other years) in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do People Look for in Someone to Date?</title>
      <link>/portfolio/what-do-people-look-for-in-someone-to-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/what-do-people-look-for-in-someone-to-date/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Joe Yates on Unsplash 
Introduction Speed dating is among one of the rising ways for people searching for a romantic relationship. When people make decisions on whether they would want to see a person again, their preferences indicate what they consider as important when picking a potentially long-term partner. This project aims to explore and explain what attribute people are looking for in a date, and can provide some insights for the prolonged interest in understanding love.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>